A Guide to the Foundation Center of New York records FA023
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program and Project Files, 1924-1999; 2
  - Programs, 1924-1998; 1
    - Donor Files, 1970-1998; B
      - The Harry Frank Guggenheim Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1)
      - The George Gund Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 34)
      - Paul and Mary Haas Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 145)
      - Evelyn and Walter Haas, Jr. Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 208)
      - Miriam and Peter Haas Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 265)
      - Walter and Elise Haas Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 322)
      - The Haigh-Scatena Foundation, 1986-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 374)
      - Crescent Porter Hale Foundation, 1987-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 402)
      - The Luke B. Hancock Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 426)
      - The Hankins Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 497)
      - The Phil Hardin Foundation, 1980-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 542)
      - The Harkness Foundation for Dance, 1991-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 609)
      - John H. and Wilhelmina D. Harland Charitable Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 624)
      - The Harris Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 690)
      - The Edward W. Hazen Foundation, 1983-1988 (Reel 78, Frame 755)
      - The HCA Foundation, 1990-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 784)
      - The Heckscher Foundation for Children, 1986-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 802)
      - Howard Heinz Endowment, 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 842)
      - Vira I. Heinz Endowment, 1987-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 914)
      - Nathan L. and Regina Herman Charitable Fund, 1986-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 968)
      - The Hershey Foundation, 1990-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1,004)
      - Hewlett-Packard Company, 1980-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1,019)
      - Corina Higginson Trust, 1985-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1,079)
      - The Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1,108)
      - Conrad N. Hilton Foundation, 1976-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1,172)
      - Paul and Annetta Himmelfarb Foundation, Inc., 1990-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1,224)
      - The Hitachi Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1,237)
      - Hoffman-LaRoche, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 1)
      - The Stewart W. and Willma C. Hoyt Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 73)
      - The Huber Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 144)
      - Hudson-Webber Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 187)
      - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 1987-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 266)
      - IBM Foundation (International Business Machine), 1981-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 386)
      - Iddings Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 489)
      - Independence Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 526)
      - The Indianapolis Foundation, 1980-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 604)
      - The International Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 693)
      - The James Irvine Foundation, 1980-1993 (Reel 79, Frame 732)
      - Ittleson Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 804)
      - Janesville Foundation, Inc., 1980-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 891)
      - Martha Holden Jennings Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 964)
      - The Mary Hillman Jennings Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 1,086)
      - The Andrew Jergens Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 1,136)
      - Jerome Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 1,198)
      - George Frederick Jewett Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 1)
      - Johnson & Johnson Family of Companies Contribution Fund, 1985-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 91)
      - The Christian A. Johnson Endeavor Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 139)
      - The Walter S. Johnson Foundation, 1982-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 233)
      - Daisy Marquis Jones Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 285)
      - The Harvey and Bernice Jones Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 369)
      - Kaiser Permanente, 1986-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 415)
      - Kalamazoo Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 447)
      - The J. M. Kaplan Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 496)
      - Ewing Marion Kauffman Foundation, 1991-1996 (Reel 80, Frame 614)
      - W. M. Keck Foundation, 1976-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 643)
      - William R. Kenan, Jr. Charitable Trust, 1981-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 782)
      - Key Foundation/Society National Bank, 1986-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 838)
      - Maria Kip Orphanage Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 852)
      - The Kiplinger Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 894)
      - F. M. Kirby Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 959)
      - Komes Foundation, 1983-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 1,072)
      - Koret Foundation, 1980-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 1,111)
      - Samuel H. Kress Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 1,218)
      - Kulas Foundation, 1980-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 1,284)
      - Albert Kunstadter Family Foundation, 1982-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 3)
      - The Stanley S. Langendorf Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 77)
      - Lannan Foundation, 1990-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 107)
      - The Laub Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 127)
      - Helen Sperry Lea Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 191)
      - The Lyda Ebert Family Foundation, 1987-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 205)
      - Levi Strauss Foundation, 1980-1990 (Reel 81, Frame 259)
      - The Lucius N. Littauer Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 388)
      - Richard Lounsbery Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 413)
      - The Joe and Emily Lowe Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 458)
      - Loyola Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 525)
      - LTV Foundation/Republic Steel Corporation Educational and Charitable Trust, 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 587)
      - The Lubrizol Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 652)
      - The Lumpkin Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 711)
      - Louis R. Lurie Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 786)
      - Miranda Lux Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 837)
      - The J. E. and L. E. Mabee Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 896)
      - James A. Macdonald Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 963)
      - Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation, 1983-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 998)
      - A. L. Mailman Family Foundation, Inc., 1990-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 1,056)
      - Margoes Foundation, 1986-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 1,069)
      - Marin Community Foundation, 1988-1994 (Reel 81, Frame 1,105)
      - The John and Mary R. Markle Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 1,137)
      - Marmot Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 1,285)
      - The J. Willard Marriott Foundation, 1988-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 1,330)
      - The George Preston Marshall Foundation, 1991 (Reel 81, Frame 1,363)
      - The S. Livingston Mather Charitable Trust, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 1)
      - Elizabeth Ring Mather and William Gwinn Mather Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 92)
      - Richard Mather Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 143)
      - The Maytag Company Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 212)
      - James J. McCann Charitable Trust - McCann Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 271)
      - Robert R. McCormick Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 331)
      - James S. McDonnell Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 460)
      - McGovern Fund for Behavioral Sciences, 1985-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 513)
      - McGregor Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 546)
      - McInerny Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 647)
      - McKesson Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 720)
      - The McKnight Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 774)
      - The McLean Contributionship, 1989-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 863)
      - The Mead Corporation, Inc., 1983-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 878)
      - The Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 928)
      - The Merck Company Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 1,077)
      - Merrill Lynch and Company Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 1,140)
      - Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 1,185)
      - Mervyn's, 1981-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 1,308)
      - Metropolitan Life Foundation, 1981-1993 (Reel 83, Frame 1)
      - Eugene and Agnes E. Meyer Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 120)
      - Fred Meyer Charitable Trust, 1984-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 234)
      - The Miller Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 317)
      - Mobil Corporation, 1982-1993 (Reel 83, Frame 378)
      - Monsanto Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 498)
      - Caroline and Roxanna Montrose Educational Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 565)
      - The Burton D. Morgan Foundation, Inc., 1991-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 581)
      - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York - J. P. Morgan, 1981-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 594)
      - Motorola Foundation, 1986-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 693)
      - M. J. Murdock Charitable Trust, 1981-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 709)
      - The Murphy Family Foundation, 1991-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 952)
      - John P. Murphy Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 968)
      - Muskegon County Community Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 1,032)
      - David and Inez Myers Fund, 1979-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 1,077)
      - National City Bank, 1986-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 1,133)
      - Nationwide Insurance Foundation, 1983-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 1,158)
      - New Hampshire Charitable Fund, 1986-1992 (Reel 83, Frame 1,200)
      - The New World Foundation, 1981-1990 (Reel 83, Frame 1,273)
      - New York Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 1)
      - The Charlotte W. Newcombe Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 89)
      - Edward John Noble Foundation, Inc., 1980-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 132)
      - The Samuel Roberts Nobel Foundation, Inc., 1983-1993 (Reel 84, Frame 211)
      - The Norcross Wildlife Foundation, Inc., 1991-1993 (Reel 84, Frame 280)
      - The Nordson Corporation Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 302)
      - Nordson Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 330)
      - North Dakota Community Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 411)
      - Northwest Area Foundation, 1980-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 459)
      - Jessie Smith Noyes Foundation, 1981-1994 (Reel 84, Frame 653)
      - The A. Lindsay and Olive B. O'Connor Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 762)
      - F. W. Olin Foundation, Inc., 1989-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 880)
      - John M. Olin Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 908)
      - The Overbrook Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 978)
      - Pacific Gas and Electric Company, 1981-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 1,001)
      - Panasonic Foundation, 1984-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 1,058)
      - Amelia Peabody Charitable Fund, 1989-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 1,113)
      - The Pfizer Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 1,142)
      - Ellis L. Phillips Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 1,212)
      - The Pinkerton Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 1,262)
      - The Pittsburgh Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 1)
      - Plough Foundation, 1990-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 77)
      - The Powell Family Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 113)
      - The Louis and Harold Price Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 184)
      - The Prudential Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 230)
      - Raytheon Charitable Foundation, 1972-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 356)
      - The Reed Foundation, Inc., 1985-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 438)
      - The Reinberger Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 552)
      - Research Corporation, 1985-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 608)
      - The Retirement Research Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 682)
      - Charles H. Revson Foundation, 1986-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 783)
      - The Christopher Reynolds Foundation, Inc., 1985-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 855)
      - Sid W. Richardson Foundation, 1972-1993 (Reel 85, Frame 905)
      - Smith Richardson Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 969)
      - Richland County Foundation, 1992 (Reel 85, Frame 1,051)
      - Fannie E. Rippel Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 1,057)
      - The Rittenhouse Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 1,126)
      - The Roberts Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 1,186)
      - Rosenberg Foundation, 1972-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 1,201)
      - The Samuel Rosenthal Foundation, 1984-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 1)
      - Samuel Rubin Foundation, 1982-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 15)
      - Helena Rubenstein Foundation, Inc., 1982-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 115)
      - Russell Sage Foundation, 1971-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 225)
      - The Fan Fox and Leslie R. Samuels Foundation, Inc., 1985-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 365)
      - The San Francisco Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 422)
      - Sasco Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 770)
      - Schering-Plough Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 855)
      - The Florence and John Schumann Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 987)
      - Walter Scott Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 1,072)
      - William E. Scott Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 1,137)
      - The Sears Family Foundation/Sears Swetland Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 1,203)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company, 1981-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 1,260)
      - Second Foundation, 1988-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 1,343)
      - The Sedgwick Foundation, 1981-1993 (Reel 87, Frame 1)
      - Sequoia Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 92)
      - Seven Springs Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 143)
      - The Sherwick Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 176)
      - Sherwin-Williams Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 265)
      - The Shubert Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 326)
      - The Sihler Mental Health Foundation, 1987-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 386)
      - The Siragusa Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 417)
      - The Sisler McFawn Foundation, 1991-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 467)
      - The Skillman Foundation, 1980-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 480)
      - May and Stanley Smith Charitable Trust, 1989-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 665)
      - The Kelvin and Eleanor Smith Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 693)
      - SmithKline Beckman Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 722)
      - The Harold B. and Dorothy A. Snyder Fund, 1989-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 815)
      - Sonoma County Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 839)
      - Southern Education Foundation, Inc., 1985-1997 (Reel 87, Frame 869)
      - The Stark County Foundation, 1983-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 919)
      - State Farm Companies Foundation, 1978-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 958)
      - Harry and Grace Steele Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 1,044)
      - David S. Stein Foundation, 1986-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 1,098)
      - The Stocker Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 1,132)
      - The Stone Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 87, Frame 1,207)
      - Hattie M. Strong Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 1)
      - Stuart Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 115)
      - The Morris Stulsaft Foundation, 1984-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 159)
      - The Frank M. Tait Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 201)
      - The Teagle Foundation, Inc., 1972-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 267)
      - T. L. L. Temple Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 346)
      - Herbert A. Templeton Foundation, 1981-1997 (Reel 88, Frame 406)
      - The Tinker Foundation, 1971-1991 (Reel 88, Frame 487)
      - Toledo Community Foundation, 1983-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 612)
      - Town Creek Foundation, Inc., 1985-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 667)
      - The Harry A. and Margaret D. Towsley Foundation, 1977-1994 (Reel 88, Frame 732)
      - Toyota USA Foundation, 1992 (Reel 88, Frame 820)
      - Transamerica Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 829)
      - The Travelers Companies Foundation, Inc./Primerica Foundation, 1983-1993 (Reel 88, Frame 878)
      - The Treu-Mart Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 1,014)
      - True North Foundation, 1990-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 1,102)
      - The Trull Foundation, 1981-1997 (Reel 88, Frame 1,121)
      - Trust Company of Georgia Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 1,209)
      - Trust Funds Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 88, Frame 1,321)
      - TRW Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 1)
      - Union Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 64)
      - The UPS Foundation, 1980-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 88)
      - UST, 1988-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 181)
      - van Ameringen Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 213)
      - Ernst D. van Loben Sels - Eleanor Slate van Loben Sels Charitable Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 299)
      - Victoria Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 380)
      - Virginia Environmental Endowment, 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 437)
      - The Laura B. Vogler Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 519)
      - The Walstrom Foundation, Inc., 1976-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 587)
      - Archie D. and Bertha H. Walker Foundation, 1985-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 645)
      - DeWitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 678)
      - Lila Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund, Inc., 1992-1993 (Reel 89, Frame 758)
      - Anna Emory Warfield Memorial Fund, Inc., 1980-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 776)
      - Washington Forrest Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 852)
      - The Washington Post Company, 1986-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 895)
      - Wells Fargo Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 914)
      - Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropological Research, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 977)
      - Weyerhaeuser Family Foundation, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 1,059)
      - The Whitaker Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 1,130)
      - Thomas H. White Charitable Trust, 1980-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 1,209)
      - The Whitehead Foundation, 1991-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 1,280)
      - G. N. Wilcox Trust Company, Limited, 1981-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 1,290)
      - Wilsey Foundation, 1989-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 1,360)
      - The Mark and Catherine Winkler Foundation, 1988-1989 (Reel 90, Frame 1)
      - The Dean Witter Foundation, 1976-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 7)
      - The Wolpert Fund, 1982-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 54)
      - Woods Charitable Fund, Inc., 1981-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 131)
      - The Farny R. Wurlitzer Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 212)
      - The Xerox Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 275)
      - The Zellerbach Family Fund, 1981-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 364)
      - Series 2.1B - Program and Project Files - Programs - Donor Files - Defunct Section (Reel 90, Frame 496)
      - The Agricultural Development Council, Inc., 1981-1988 (Reel 90, Frame 497)
      - Amax Foundation, Inc., 1981-1998 (Reel 90, Frame 526)
      - AmeriTrust Company, 1983-1998 (Reel 90, Frame 603)
      - Amfac Foundation, 1981-1988 (Reel 90, Frame 646)
      - Ampex Corporation, 1985-1998 (Reel 90, Frame 683)
      - The April Trust, 1985-1988 (Reel 90, Frame 722)
      - The Vincent Astor Foundation, 1983-1998 (Reel 90, Frame 752)
      - The Bancroft, Avery & McAlister Foundation, 1989-1998 (Reel 90, Frame 834)
      - Battelle Memorial Institute Foundation, 1977-1983 (Reel 90, Frame 864)
      - The Edna and Jack Belasco Foundation, 1985-1993 (Reel 90, Frame 893)
      - Bell Atlantic/C & P Telephone, 1989-1998 (Reel 90, Frame 940)
      - Chemical Bank, 1980-1998 (Reel 90, Frame 956)
      - Conoco Inc., 1981-1987 (Reel 90, Frame 1,101)
      - Consolidated Capital Companies, 1984-1990 (Reel 90, Frame 1,144)
      - Queene Ferry Coonely Foundation, Inc., 1981-1994 (Reel 90, Frame 1,162)
      - Crocker National Bank Foundation, 1982-1987 (Reel 90, Frame 1,301)
      - The Dakin Fund, 1984-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 1,327)
      - Del Monte Corporation, 1985-1992 (Reel 91, Frame 1)
      - The Aaron Diamond Foundation, Inc., 1987-1997 (Reel 91, Frame 30)
      - Doric Development Inc., 1989-1993 (Reel 91, Frame 161)
      - Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation, 1985-1989 (Reel 91, Frame 175)
      - Field Corporation Fund, 1981-1991 (Reel 91, Frame 190)
      - The Field Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 91, Frame 225)
      - First Interstate Bank of California Foundation, 1981-1997 (Reel 91, Frame 280)
      - Fisher Fund - c/o Pittsburgh Foundation, 1981-1983 (Reel 91, Frame 354)
      - The Janet and Mortimer Fleishhacker Foundation, 1986-1996 (Reel 91, Frame 370)
      - The Parker B. Francis Foundation, 1981-1989 (Reel 91, Frame 382)
      - Garvey Foundation, 1981-1993 (Reel 91, Frame 420)
      - Eva Gebhard-Gourgaud Foundation, 1981-1989 (Reel 91, Frame 466)
      - Getty Oil Company, 1982-1984 (Reel 91, Frame 516)
      - Glen Eagles Foundation, 1991-1997 (Reel 91, Frame 535)
      - Home Savings of America, 1989-1996 (Reel 91, Frame 587)
      - Cecil Howard Charitable Trust, 1985-1994 (Reel 91, Frame 604)
      - INA Foundation, 1981 (Reel 91, Frame 630)
      - International Telephone & Telegraph Corporation, 1981-1995 (Reel 91, Frame 635)
      - JDR 3rd Fund, 1981 (Reel 91, Frame 675)
      - Kokoro Foundation, 1994-1997 (Reel 91, Frame 680)
      - Kraft General Foods Foundation, 1981-1990 (Reel 91, Frame 698)
      - The Kroc Foundation, 1981-1991 (Reel 91, Frame 760)
      - Lasdon Foundation, 1986-1995 (Reel 91, Frame 794)
      - The Lavanburg-Corner House, 1981-1996 (Reel 91, Frame 840)
      - Leaseway Transportation Corporation, 1986-1987 (Reel 91, Frame 973)
      - George A. Macpherson Fund, 1976-1979 (Reel 91, Frame 983)
      - Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust, 1989-1997 (Reel 91, Frame 990)
      - The Marsden Foundation, 1981-1989 (Reel 91, Frame 1,039)
      - The Martin Foundation, 1988-1996 (Reel 91, Frame 1,070)
      - Phillips Petroleum Foundation, Inc., 1982-1996 (Reel 91, Frame 1,083)
      - James Picker Foundation, 1985-1986 (Reel 91, Frame 1,196)
      - The Polk Foundation, 1976-1993 (Reel 91, Frame 1,209)
      - Henry A. Rafsky Research Fund, Inc., 1981-1993 (Reel 91, Frame 1,235)
      - Reliance Electric Company Charitable, Scientific and Educational Trust, 1985-1995 (Reel 91, Frame 1,253)
      - Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music, Inc., 1980-1983 (Reel 91, Frame 1,300)
      - Benjamin Rosenthal Foundation, Inc., 1981-1988 (Reel 91, Frame 1,326)
      - Stanley Roth, Sr. Charitable Trust, 1985-1987 (Reel 92, Frame 1)
      - Sachem Fund, 1981-1987 (Reel 92, Frame 16)
      - Saint Ann Foundation, 1980-1991 (Reel 92, Frame 24)
      - The Salomon Brothers Foundation, Inc., 1980-1982 (Reel 92, Frame 157)
      - The Schultz Foundation & The William Lightfoot Schultz Foundation, 1981-1995 (Reel 92, Frame 166)
      - Security Pacific Foundation, 1972-1992 (Reel 92, Frame 212)
      - The Shalan Foundation, 1988-1992 (Reel 92, Frame 266)
      - Signet Bank, 1996-1997 (Reel 92, Frame 289)
      - The L. J. Skaggs and Mary C. Skaggs Foundation, 1981-1994 (Reel 92, Frame 301)
      - The Albert and Marie Steinert Foundation, 1981-1992 (Reel 92, Frame 366)
      - Margaret Dorrance Strawbridge Foundation, 1981-1987 (Reel 92, Frame 419)
      - The Treuhaft Foundation, 1980-1991 (Reel 92, Frame 427)
      - United Brands Foundation, 1972-1985 (Reel 92, Frame 484)
      - United States Leasing Capital, 1982-1996 (Reel 92, Frame 524)
      - Van Dorn Foundation, 1988-1992 (Reel 92, Frame 590)
      - The Warner and Swasey Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 92, Frame 599)
      - Paul L. and Phyllis Wattis Foundation, 1981-1988 (Reel 92, Frame 631)
      - Western Electric Fund, 1981-1984 (Reel 92, Frame 654)
      - Westfield-Wallace Fund, Inc., 1981 (Reel 92, Frame 690)
      - Robert C. Wheeler Foundation, 1989-1994 (Reel 92, Frame 708)
      - White Consolidated Industries, Inc., 1989-1996 (Reel 92, Frame 721)
      - John Hay Whitney Foundation, 1981-1983 (Reel 92, Frame 749)
    - Foundation Correspondence, 1924-1979; C
      The correspondence in this series is arranged in two alphabetical runs: United States, 1924-1979; and Foreign, 1956-1975.
      Series 2.1C consists of correspondence with non-profit organizations.
      - United States - Iowa, 1926-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        The Maytag Company, Public Relations Department, Newton, Iowa Betty Dickinson, (2.5 x 3.5)", black and white J. D. Cox, (2.5 x 3.5)", black and white
        See also Reel 95, Frame 0313.
      - United States - New York - New York Community Trust, 1945-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)